How are you feeling today?
你今天感觉怎么样？
If your head’s in a spin because you’ve had a bad night's sleep, or you’re hungover, or maybe you’ve just got too much to do, the chances are you’re not in the best of moods.
如果因为昨晚没睡好、宿醉未醒，或是手头事情太多而头晕目眩，那么你的心情大概率不会太好。
If everything seems like an effort and you have a negative attitude, the last thing you want to be told it to ‘be positive!’
要是做什么事都觉得费劲，心态也比较消极，那你最不想听到的话，恐怕就是“乐观点”了！
But having this mindset could have more benefits than you think.
但保持积极的心态，带来的好处可能比你想象的要多得多。
Of course, developing a positive attitude is easier said than done – it doesn’t come naturally to everyone.
当然，培养积极心态说起来容易做起来难——并非每个人都能天生拥有这种心态。
When you’re feeling down in the dumps, it is hard to be optimistic.
当你情绪低落时，想要乐观起来并不容易。
But a study in the US has found that people who are optimists are more likely to live longer than those who have a more negative approach to life.
但美国的一项研究发现，乐观主义者比生活态度更消极的人更有可能长寿。
It revealed the likelihood of positive people living to the age of 85 or more to be higher.
研究显示，心态积极的人活到85岁及以上的概率更高。
So, maybe the thought of a longer life might encourage you to have a more hopeful outlook on life.
所以，或许一想到能更长寿，你就会更愿意用充满希望的眼光看待生活。
The study concluded that optimists may find it easier to control emotions and get less stressed.
这项研究得出结论：乐观的人或许更容易控制情绪，感受到的压力也更小。
And as stress impacts on the immune system, it’s possible that optimists cope better with infections.
而由于压力会影响免疫系统，乐观主义者可能更善于应对感染。
Professor Lewina Lee from Boston University School of Medicine, who worked on the study, told the BBC that: "Our findings speak to the possibility that raising levels of optimism may promote longevity and healthy ageing."
参与该研究的波士顿大学医学院教授勒维娜·李向英国广播公司表示：“我们的研究结果表明，提升乐观程度有可能促进长寿和健康老龄化。”
And she advises that pessimists could benefit from doing things like imagining a future where everything turns out well.
她还建议，悲观主义者可以尝试一些方法，比如想象一个一切都向好发展的未来，这会对他们有所帮助。
But if you’re a ‘glass half empty’ type of person, could seeing the world through rose-tinted glasses work for you?
但如果你是那种“杯子里的水只剩一半”的悲观主义者，用过于乐观的眼光看待世界对你来说会有用吗？
Accepting that we all have problems and that we’re not all the same helps us to get a grip on our emotions.
接受每个人都会遇到难题、每个人都各有不同的事实，有助于我们掌控自己的情绪。
Some people say it’s best to celebrate the positives and not dwell on the negative parts of our lives.
有人说，最好的做法是多肯定生活中的积极面，不要一味纠结于消极的部分。
People have being giving the BBC their personal advice on keeping a healthy and positive approach to life: Vicki Siska says "Music feeds my soul, a sense of humour keeps things in perspective, and I have good friends who love and care for me."
人们纷纷向英国广播公司分享了自己保持健康积极生活态度的个人心得：维基·西斯卡说：“音乐滋养我的灵魂，幽默感帮我正确看待事物，我还有一群爱我、关心我的好朋友。”
And Pippa Kennedy says "being grateful for what you have - and lots of chocolate - helps!"
皮帕·肯尼迪则表示：“对自己所拥有的一切心怀感恩——再加上多吃点巧克力——会很有帮助！”
The saying goes that ‘a healthy body leads a healthy mind’ which is probably why other people have recommended doing yoga and meditation as well as staying fit and healthy to help maintain a positive outlook on life.
有句谚语说“健全的精神寓于健康的身体”，这或许就是为什么还有人建议，通过练习瑜伽、冥想以及保持身体健康，来帮助维持积极的生活态度。